http://moduloc-intl.com/privacy-policy/

Site Navigation HomeProductsView All ProductsHot Metal DetectorsRemote Hot MetalFixed Hot MetalScanning Hot MetalPyrometer SensorsPhotocellsLaser DetectorsDistance Measuring LasersDetection Laser SensorsLaser Velocity MetersLaser Thickness GaugesLaser ProjectorsFlatness MeasurementProximity SensorsMetal DetectorsApplicationsPartnersCompanyContactHomeProductsView All ProductsHot Metal DetectorsRemote Hot MetalFixed Hot MetalScanning Hot MetalPyrometer SensorsPhotocellsLaser DetectorsDistance Measuring LasersDetection Laser SensorsLaser Velocity MetersLaser Thickness GaugesLaser ProjectorsFlatness MeasurementProximity SensorsMetal DetectorsApplicationsPartnersCompanyContactHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyAt Moduloc we are committed to preserving your right to privacy. We want our visitors to be fully aware of the personal information we collect through our website. The statement below describes the manner in which we collect, use, disclose and manage your personal information.Personal Information CollectionYou do not need to provide any personal information to us when visiting our website. The only personal information we collect through our website is the information you may voluntarily provide to us through the “contact” section of the website or if you choose to send an email to an employee at Moduloc.We may automatically collect general anonymous information related to your use of our Website, such as the date and time you visit the Website and the pages you visit on the Website. Our servers may also automatically collect information about the type of browser you use and the name of your Internet Service Provider. In addition, we may collect “cookie” information from your browser to identify your computer and provide us with a record of your visits to our Website. We may use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Personal Information UsageAny personal information you provide to us when you send us an email is used solely to identify who you are and to respond to the purpose for which you submitted the message.Personal Information DisclosureModuloc will not transfer, sell or otherwise disclose any of your personal information to any third party without your prior written consent. We may disclose your personal information to third parties that may administer or manage on-line services on our behalf.LinksThis website may contain links to other sites. Moduloc does not assume any responsibility or liability for any communications or materials available at those linked sites. All links are provided for your convenience only; they are not an endorsement or referral by our company.Security of Personal InformationWe will maintain your personal information in secure data storage to safeguard it from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We will maintain the strict confidentiality of all personal information collected, and will only disclose such information on a confidential basis to employees of Moduloc who require such information for the purposes set out above.We will only keep your personal information for as long as it remains necessary or relevant for the purposes stated above or as otherwise required by law. Email communications between Moduloc and yourself may not be secure. We suggest that you encrypt all email to increase the security of your communications with our company.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 05/05/2016.ContactIf you would like to request access to personal information about you, request a correction to information about you or have questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at:44 (0)143 817 792
sales@moduloc-intl.com22b London Rd, Woolmer Green
Knebworth, SG3 6JPRequest Product InformationName*CompanyEmail*
PhoneCommentsNameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Request Product InformationName*CompanyEmail*
PhoneCommentsPhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
